awesomedl.com 2017-12-12

# Panel privacy | Freerice.com

## FREERICE.COM PRIVACY POLICY

Freerice.com (the "Site") and its operator, World Food Programme, (collectively "we" or "us") are committed to protecting your privacy on the Internet. This privacy policy tells you about the types of information that may be collected from you while you use the site, how that information will be used, who can see it and your rights to review and request changes to it. 

## What information does Freerice.com collect and how is it used?

#### Non-personally identifiable information 

When you access the Site, certain information such as your Internet protocol (IP) address, navigation through the Site, browser used and time spent, along with other similar information, may be stored on our servers and on third party servers. This information is never connected with any personal information collected on the site and is treated confidentially. It is collected only to help us understand the preferences of our visitors and improve their experiences on the Site. 

#### Use of cookies 

We may occasionally use cookies, pieces of data stored on a user's hard drive containing information about the user, to identify your computer on future visits to the site. This allows us to save your preferences and avoid asking you the same questions we asked on your previous visits and will never be linked to any information that would allow you to be personally identified. 

You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although, if you do, you may not be able to use certain features on the site and may be required to re-enter information more frequently to use certain services on the Site. 

#### Personally identifiable information

Freerice.com is accessible to everyone. However, if you to want to use all of the features of the Site, you need to sign up for an account. When you sign up for an account, we will ask you for an email address, user name and date of birth. IF YOU ARE UNDER 14 YEARS OLD, YOU MAY NOT SUBMIT YOUR REAL NAME FOR YOUR USERNAME AND YOU MAY ONLY SUBMIT YOUR PARENT’S EMAIL ADDRESS. This information will allow you to sign in to the Site every time you return so that you can accrue grains of rice over multiple visits, post comments, and interact with other users. If you are 14 years of age or older, you will also have the option of receiving emails from WFP at the email address you submit. WFP WILL NOT SHARE ANY OF THIS INFORMATION WITH ANY THIRD PARTIES, EXCEPT FOR THE PURPOSE OF ADMINISTRATING THE GAME. 

You also have the option of voluntarily submitting additional personal information to build a “profile” on the Site; this information will include a name, photo, personal website URL and any other form of personal information that you may choose to submit. IF YOU ARE UNDER 14 YEARS OLD, YOU MAY NOT SUBMIT ANY INFORMATION THAT COULD BE USED TO IDENTIFY OR CONTACT YOU. The purpose of a profile is to allow you to network with other users of the Site and can be viewed by other users of the site; WFP will not transmit any information you submit for your profile to anyone other than users of the Site. 

#### Children’s information

We do not collect any personal information from anyone under the age of 14. If we find out that a user who is under the age of 14 has submitted personal information to the Site, including any information that might be used to identify or contact the user, we will delete it immediately. We reserve the right to do so without notice to the user. If you suspect or know that a user under the age of 14 has submitted any personal information on the Site, [please contact us](mailto:WFP.Freerice@wfp.org) with the subject line “Report: Under 14 Player”. 

## Who can see the information that’s collected on Freerice.com?

We take reasonable steps to protect all of your information, but we assume no responsibility for the security of the information you submit on the Site. Except as noted above, we do not sell or share any of your information with any third parties. However, other users of the Site will be able to see any information that you choose to make public on your profile, in addition to your username. 

## How can you view and delete the information collected by Freerice.com? 

#### Username and password 

You can have your username and password sent to your email address at any time. You may change your password, as well as other details, by signing into your account and selecting "My Account", "Edit Profile" 

Your username cannot be altered. 

#### Profile information

You can view, edit and delete any information on your profile, apart from your username, by signing into your account and selecting "My Account", "Edit Profile". We will not store any deleted information, or previous versions of edited information. If you would like to delete your entire profile or account, [please contact us](mailto:WFP.Freerice@wfp.org)

#### Email address

If you would like to have your email address deleted from our records, [please contact us](mailto:WFP.Freerice@wfp.org)

## How will I know if this privacy policy has changed?

This policy is effective as of [24/09/2010]. Changes to this privacy policy will be posted here (freerice.com/about/privacy ). We will not be actively contacting you with updates, so please check back frequently for any changes. 

## Who can I contact with questions about this policy?

Please email us: [WFP.Freerice (at) wfp.org](mailto:WFP.Freerice@wfp.org)
